Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 6 and District 6 Locals, 1936-1995 UE.4.1.6
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 6 Locals, 2.
  - Local 609
    - Local 609 710 Forms, 1948-1969 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Local 610
    - Local 610 Officers Lists, October 1, 1941 - November 1, 1944 (Box 7, Folder 64)
    - Local 610 Contract, May 1942 (Box 7, Folder 65)
    - Local 610 Membership Resolutions, March 14, 1941 - March 30, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 66)
      - Resolution Regarding Wages, March 14, 1941; 1. (Box 7, Folder 66, Item 1)
      - Resolution Regarding Strike Authorization, March 14, 1941; 2. (Box 7, Folder 66, Item 2)
      - Resolution Regarding Anti-War Movement, 1941; 3. (Box 7, Folder 66, Item 3)
      - Resolution Regarding Wages, March 30, 1949; 4. (Box 7, Folder 66, Item 4)
    - Local 610 Harold Briney Incoming Correspondence, January 10, 1951 - January 10, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 67)
      - Neil Brant Regarding Dismissals, National Labor Relations Board and War Labor Board, February 11, 1943; 1. (Box 7, Folder 67, Item 1)
      - Brant Regarding War Labor Board and Local 610 Westinghouse Air Brake Company Collective Bargaining, April 29, 1943; 2. (Box 7, Folder 67, Item 2)
      - Brant Regarding Executive Order 9240, Overtime and War Labor Board, May 25, 1943; 3. (Box 7, Folder 67, Item 3)
      - Julius Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, January 10, 1951; 4. (Box 7, Folder 67, Item 4)
      - Albert Fitzgerald Telegram, October 24, 1947; 5. (Box 7, Folder 67, Item 5)
      - Stanley Loney Regarding IUE Inter-Union Rivalry, February 4, 1953; 6. (Box 7, Folder 67, Item 6)
      - James Matles Letter, February 1, 1943; 7. (Box 7, Folder 67, Item 7)
      - Matles Telegram Regarding National Labor Relations Board Election and Irwin Westinghouse, September 8, 1950; 8. (Box 7, Folder 67, Item 8)
      - Matles Regarding District 6 Council, July 11, 1950; 9. (Box 7, Folder 67, Item 9)
      - Matles Regarding Lynn, Schenectady and Erie General Electric and IUE Inter-Union Rivalry, August 21, 1951; 10. (Box 7, Folder 67, Item 10)
      - Matles Regarding Finances, September 11, 1952; 11. (Box 7, Folder 67, Item 11)
      - Matles Regarding Finances, East Pittsburgh Westinghouse and IUE Inter-Union Rivalry, September 23, 1952; 12. (Box 7, Folder 67, Item 12)
      - Matles Regarding Dues Check-Off, May 11, 1953; 13. (Box 7, Folder 67, Item 13)
      - Matles Regarding Finances, August 3, 1953; 14-15. (Box 7, Folder 67, Item 14-15.)
      - Edward Matthews Regarding Wages with Idele Wilson Letter, April 16, 1945; 16. (Box 7, Folder 67, Item 16)
      - Matthews Regarding Veterans and Apprenticeship, June 26, 1945; 17. (Box 7, Folder 67, Item 17)
      - Matthews Regarding Veterans and Apprenticeship, July 16, 1945; 18. (Box 7, Folder 67, Item 18)
      - Porter Mechling Regarding Finances with April 16, 1945, Check, February 17, 1950; 19. (Box 7, Folder 67, Item 19)
      - F. H. Wood Regarding Dismissals and Anti-Communism, January 10, 1955; 20. (Box 7, Folder 67, Item 20)
    - Local 610 Harold Briney Outgoing Correspondence, October 23, 1941 - August 7, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 68)
      - Briney Telegram to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Local 610 Officers, October 23, 1941; 1. (Box 7, Folder 68, Item 1)
      - Briney Telegram to James Matles Regarding Dismissals and Arbitration, November 7, 1941; 2. (Box 7, Folder 68, Item 2)
      - Briney to Tom Wright Regarding Address Change, October 17, 1942; 3. (Box 7, Folder 68, Item 3)
      - Briney to Matles Regarding Grievances, Westinghouse Air Brake Company Strike, Racism, Factionalism and Unemployment, July 20, 1943; 4. (Box 7, Folder 68, Item 4)
      - Briney to Edward Matthews Regarding Apprenticeship and Local 610 WABCO Collective Bargaining, July 20, 1945; 5. (Box 7, Folder 68, Item 5)
      - Briney Telegram to Matles Regarding Local 610 WABCO and Union Switch Contracts, June 26, 1948; 6. (Box 7, Folder 68, Item 6)
      - Briney to Matles Regarding Staff Members, June 29, 1950; 7. (Box 7, Folder 68, Item 7)
      - Briney to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances and Irwin Westinghouse, March 16, 1951; 8. (Box 7, Folder 68, Item 8)
      - Briney to Emspak Regarding UE Fighting Fund and Unemployment, February 7, 1952; 9. (Box 7, Folder 68, Item 9)
      - Briney to Emspak Regarding Factonalism and District 6 Council with Briney Letter to Fitzgerald, October 1, 1952; 10. (Box 7, Folder 68, Item 10)
      - Briney to Fitzgerald Regarding Finances, East Pittsburgh Westinghouse, Unemployment, IUE Inter-Union Rivalry and Union Switch and Signal, April 28, 1953; 11. (Box 7, Folder 68, Item 11)
      - Briney to Matles Regarding Finances, July 24, 1953; 12. (Box 7, Folder 68, Item 12)
      - Briney to Stanley Loney Regarding Per Capita Dues, August 7, 1953; 13. (Box 7, Folder 68, Item 13)
      - Briney Telegram to Matles Regarding Westinghouse and General Electric, undated; 14. (Box 7, Folder 68, Item 14)
    - Local 610 Clyde Johnson Incoming Correspondence, June 12, 1946 - February 17, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 69)
      - William Cahn Regarding Publicity, November 15, 1946; 1. (Box 7, Folder 69, Item 1)
      - Cahn Regarding Publicity, January 20, 1947; 2. (Box 7, Folder 69, Item 2)
      - Julius Emspak Regarding Philadelphia UE Strike, September 23, 1946; 3. (Box 7, Folder 69, Item 3)
      - Emspak Regarding Foreman and Apprentices Organization, September 27, 1946; 4. (Box 7, Folder 69, Item 4)
      - Emspak Regarding Workmen's Compensation, September 12, 1947; 5. (Box 7, Folder 69, Item 5)
      - Emspak Telegram Regarding United Mine Workers of America, undated; 6. (Box 7, Folder 69, Item 6)
      - Albert Fitzgerald Telegram, November 12, 1947; 7. (Box 7, Folder 69, Item 7)
      - James Matles Telegram, June 12, 1946; 8. (Box 7, Folder 69, Item 8)
      - Matles Regarding Staff Members, June 19, 1946; 9. (Box 7, Folder 69, Item 9)
      - Matles Regarding Staff Finances, July 2, 1946; 10. (Box 7, Folder 69, Item 10)
      - Matles Regarding White Collar Workers, July 29, 1946; 11. (Box 7, Folder 69, Item 11)
      - Matles Regarding White Collar Workers, August 6, 1946; 12. (Box 7, Folder 69, Item 12)
      - Matles Regarding Veterans, October 1, 1946; 13. (Box 7, Folder 69, Item 13)
      - Matles Regarding General Railway Signal, November 20, 1946; 14. (Box 7, Folder 69, Item 14)
      - Selma Trauber, Secretary to Matles, Regarding Local 610 Westinghouse Air Brake Company Collective Bargaining, April 11, 1947; 15. (Box 7, Folder 69, Item 15)
      - Trauber, Secretary to Matles, Telegram, April 14, 1947; 16. (Box 7, Folder 69, Item 16)
      - Matles Telegram Regarding Local 610 WABCO Collective Bargaining and White Collar Workers, June 16, 1947; 17. (Box 7, Folder 69, Item 17)
      - Matles Letter, September 18, 1947; 18. (Box 7, Folder 69, Item 18)
      - Trauber, Secretary to Matles, Letter, October 17, 1947; 19. (Box 7, Folder 69, Item 19)
      - Matles Letter, October 22, 1947; 20. (Box 7, Folder 69, Item 20)
      - Matles Regarding Holidays, February 17, 1948; 21. (Box 7, Folder 69, Item 21)
      - Edward Matthews Regarding WABCO, September 25, 1946; 22. (Box 7, Folder 69, Item 22)
      - Matthews Regarding WABCO, October 1, 1946; 23. (Box 7, Folder 69, Item 23)
      - Don Pinkston Regarding House Un-American Activities Committee, August 18, 1947; 24. (Box 7, Folder 69, Item 24)
      - Tom Wright Regarding Publicity, November 14, 1947; 25. (Box 7, Folder 69, Item 25)
    - Local 610 Clyde Johnson Outgoing Correspondence, June 10 - November 27, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 70)
      - Johnson Telegram to James Matles Regarding Staff Members, June 10, 1946; 1. (Box 7, Folder 70, Item 1)
      - Johnson to Matles Regarding Staff Members, June 12, 1946; 2. (Box 7, Folder 70, Item 2)
      - Johnson to Matles Regarding Staff Members, June 16, 1946; 3. (Box 7, Folder 70, Item 3)
      - Johnson to Matles Regarding White Collar Workers and Association of Westinghouse Salaried Employees, July 24, 1946; 4. (Box 7, Folder 70, Item 4)
      - Johnson to Matles Regarding White Collar Workers and Organization at Westinghouse Air Brake Company and Union Switch and Signal, July 31, 1946; 5. (Box 7, Folder 70, Item 5)
      - Johnson to Seymour Linfield Regarding Arbitration, Veterans and White Collar Workers, August 2, 1946; 6. (Box 7, Folder 70, Item 6)
      - Johnson to Matles Regarding Arbitrations, Veterans and Vacations, August 3, 1946; 7. (Box 7, Folder 70, Item 7)
      - Johnson to Julius Emspak Regarding Political Action Committee, August 27, 1946; 8. (Box 7, Folder 70, Item 8)
      - Johnson to Emspak Regarding PAC, August 30, 1946; 9. (Box 7, Folder 70, Item 9)
      - Johnson Telegram to Emspak Regarding District 1 Defense Committee, September 18, 1946; 10. (Box 7, Folder 70, Item 10)
      - Johnson to Matles Regarding 1946 UE Convention and Foremen Organization, September 18, 1946; 11. (Box 7, Folder 70, Item 11)
      - Johnson to Edward Matthews Regarding WABCO, September 19, 1946; 12. (Box 7, Folder 70, Item 12)
      - Johnson to Emspak Regarding UE Constitution and PAC, September 27, 1946; 13. (Box 7, Folder 70, Item 13)
      - Johnson to Matles Regarding General Railway Signal Organization, October 28, 1946; 14. (Box 7, Folder 70, Item 14)
      - Johnson to Matles Regarding General Railway Signal Organization, November 13, 1946; 15. (Box 7, Folder 70, Item 15)
      - Johnson to Tom Wright Regarding Publicity, November 13, 1946; 16. (Box 7, Folder 70, Item 16)
      - Johnson to Emspak Regarding PAC, November 21, 1946; 17. (Box 7, Folder 70, Item 17)
      - Johnson to Robert Lamb Regarding Political Action and 1946 Election, November 27, 1946; 18. (Box 7, Folder 70, Item 18)
    - Local 610 Clyde Johnson Outgoing Correspondence, December 3, 1946 - February 10, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 71)
      - Johnson Telegram to Julius Emspak Regarding Portal to Portal Pay, December 3, 1946; 1. (Box 7, Folder 71, Item 1)
      - Johnson Telegram to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding United Mine Workers Strike, December 5, 1946; 2. (Box 7, Folder 71, Item 2)
      - Johnson to Emspak Regarding Political Action Committee, December 11, 1946; 3. (Box 7, Folder 71, Item 3)
      - Johnson Telegram to Fitzgerald Regarding Stewards Council Meeting, December 13, 1946; 4. (Box 7, Folder 71, Item 4)
      - Johnson to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, January 13, 1947; 5. (Box 7, Folder 71, Item 5)
      - Johnson Telegram to William Cahn Regarding Publicity, January 20, 1947; 6. (Box 7, Folder 71, Item 6)
      - Johnson to Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism, Local 613 and Allis-Chalmers Strike, February 17, 1947; 7. (Box 7, Folder 71, Item 7)
      - Johnson to Emspak Regarding Finances, February 1947; 8. (Box 7, Folder 71, Item 8)
      - Johnson Telegram to James Matles Regarding Local 610 Westinghouse Air Brake Company Collective Bargaining, April 10, 1947; 9. (Box 7, Folder 71, Item 9)
      - Johnson to Matles Regarding Local 610 WABCO Collective Bargaining, April 10, 1947; 10. (Box 7, Folder 71, Item 10)
      - Johnson to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, June 2, 1947; 11. (Box 7, Folder 71, Item 11)
      - Johnson to Matles Regarding Grievances and Time Study, June 17, 1947; 12. (Box 7, Folder 71, Item 12)
      - Johnson Telegram to Matles Regarding Factionalism and 1947 UE Convention Delegates, June 27, 1947; 13. (Box 7, Folder 71, Item 13)
      - Johnson Telegram to Russ Nixon Regarding Supplies and PAC, July 24, 1947; 14. (Box 7, Folder 71, Item 14)
      - Johnson to Matles Regarding House Un-American Activities Committee, August 13, 1947; 15. (Box 7, Folder 71, Item 15)
      - Johnson to Emspak Regarding Finances with Receipt, October 1, 1947; 16. (Box 7, Folder 71, Item 16)
      - Johnson to Emspak Regarding Workmen's Compensation, October 6, 1947; 17. (Box 7, Folder 71, Item 17)
      - Johnson to Matles Regarding Arbitration, Automation and Time Study, October 9, 1947; 18. (Box 7, Folder 71, Item 18)
      - Johnson to Emspak Regardeing Carl Marzani Defense Fund with November 7, 1947, Emspak Letter to Civil Rights Congress, October 29, 1947; 19. (Box 7, Folder 71, Item 19)
      - Johnson Telegram to Fitzgerald Regarding Membership Meeting, November 12, 1947; 20. (Box 7, Folder 71, Item 20)
      - Johnson to Fitzgerald Regarding Membership Meeting, Taft-Hartley and Westinghouse Collective Bargaining, November 13, 1947; 21. (Box 7, Folder 71, Item 21)
      - Johnson to Tom Wright Regarding Publicity, November 13, 1947; 22. (Box 7, Folder 71, Item 22)
      - Johnson to Matles Regarding United Steelworkers of America and Association of Catholic Trade Unionists with December 9, 1947, Pittsburgh Post-Gazette Clipping, December 10, 1947; 23. (Box 7, Folder 71, Item 23)
      - Johnson to Fitzgerald Regarding Central Labor Delegates Election, Factionalism and Taft-Hartley Affidavits, December 15, 1947; 24. (Box 7, Folder 71, Item 24)
    - Local 610 Clyde Johnson Outgoing Correspondence, January 13 - February 10, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 72)
      - Johnson to James Matles Regarding Local 610 WABCO Collective Bargaining and Holidays with Johnson Letter to W. C. Landis, January 13, 1948; 1. (Box 7, Folder 72, Item 1)
      - Johnson to Matles Regarding Holidays and Grievances, February 10, 1948; 2. (Box 7, Folder 72, Item 2)
    - Local 610 Robert Kirkwood Incoming Correspondence, June 28, 1949 - February 24, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 73)
      - Janet Barish Regarding Staff Finances, June 28, 1949; 1. (Box 7, Folder 73, Item 1)
      - Barish Regarding Address, November 29, 1949; 2. (Box 7, Folder 73, Item 2)
      - Barish Regarding Mailing List, February 1, 1950; 3. (Box 7, Folder 73, Item 3)
      - Barish Regarding Staff Finances, October 9, 1950; 4. (Box 7, Folder 73, Item 4)
      - William Cahn Regarding Staff Finances, April 19, 1950; 5. (Box 7, Folder 73, Item 5)
      - Fannie Cohn, Secretary to William Cahn, Regarding Publicity and IUE Inter-Union Rivalry, May 5, 1950; 6. (Box 7, Folder 73, Item 6)
      - Emspak Regarding Mailing List, July 19, 1951; 7. (Box 7, Folder 73, Item 7)
      - Emspak Regarding Finances, July 21, 1953; 8. (Box 7, Folder 73, Item 8)
      - Emspak Regarding Finances, July 29, 1953; 9. (Box 7, Folder 73, Item 9)
      - Emspak Regarding Finances, February 17, 1954; 10. (Box 7, Folder 73, Item 10)
      - Emspak Regarding Finances and Briney & Wright Dismissals, December 28, 1955; 11. (Box 7, Folder 73, Item 11)
      - James Matles Regarding Pensions, Local 610 Westinghouse Air Brake Company Contract and IUE Inter-Union Rivalry, February 23, 1950; 12. (Box 7, Folder 73, Item 12)
      - Matles Regarding IUE Inter-Union Rivalry, July 23, 1952; 13. (Box 7, Folder 73, Item 13)
      - Matles Regarding Local 601 Nuttall Westinghouse Strike, July 29, 1952; 14. (Box 7, Folder 73, Item 14)
      - Matles Regarding Finances, June 17, 1953; 15. (Box 7, Folder 73, Item 15)
      - Matles Letter, December 10, 1954; 16. (Box 7, Folder 73, Item 16)
      - Matles Letter, January 14, 1955; 17. (Box 7, Folder 73, Item 17)
      - Matles Telegram Regarding Reservations, January 17, 1955; 18. (Box 7, Folder 73, Item 18)
      - Matles Regarding Matusow Affidavit, January 31, 1955; 19. (Box 7, Folder 73, Item 19)
      - Matles Letter, February 24, 1955; 20. (Box 7, Folder 73, Item 20)
    - Local 610 Robert Kirkwood Incoming Correspondence, November 3, 1952 - September 13, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 74)
      - Edward Matthews Letter, September 19, 1952; 1. (Box 7, Folder 74, Item 1)
      - Matthews Regarding Wages and Hours, November 3, 1952; 2. (Box 7, Folder 74, Item 2)
      - Russ Nixon Regarding FBI, December 6, 1954; 3. (Box 7, Folder 74, Item 3)
      - David Ratner Memo Regarding Finances, March 21, 1951; 4. (Box 7, Folder 74, Item 4)
      - Unsigned Letter Regarding Convention Tours, September 13, 1954; 5. (Box 7, Folder 74, Item 5)
    - Local 610 Robert Kirkwood Outgoing Correspondence, August 11, 1948 - August 29, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 75)
      - Kirkwood to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism and Anti-Communism with The Eye Opener, August 11, 1948; 1. (Box 7, Folder 75, Item 1)
      - Kirkwood to Fitzgerald Regarding Atomic Energy Commission and General Electric, November 17, 1948; 2. (Box 7, Folder 75, Item 2)
      - Kirkwood to James Matles, January 10, 1949; 3. (Box 7, Folder 75, Item 3)
      - Kirkwood to Julius Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, February 7, 1949; 4. (Box 7, Folder 75, Item 4)
      - Kirkwood to Matles Regarding Westinghouse Conference Board, February 10, 1949; 5. (Box 7, Folder 75, Item 5)
      - Kirkwood to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, March 9, 1949; 6. (Box 7, Folder 75, Item 6)
      - Kirkwood to Fitzgerald Regarding Wages, March 30, 1949; 7. (Box 7, Folder 75, Item 7)
      - Kirkwood to Matles Regarding Die Sinkers and United Auto Workers Inter-Union Rivalry, March 30, 1949; 8. (Box 7, Folder 75, Item 8)
      - Kirkwood to Philip Murray Regarding Congress of Industrial Organizations and Wages, March 30, 1949; 9. (Box 7, Folder 75, Item 9)
      - Kirkwood to Matles Regarding Local 610 Westinghouse Air Brake Company Collective Bargaining, Veterans, Vacations and Pattern Makers Inter-Union Rivalry, April 8, 1949; 10. (Box 7, Folder 75, Item 10)
      - Kirkwood to Matles Regarding Local 610 WABCO Collective Bargaining, May 3, 1949; 11. (Box 7, Folder 75, Item 11)
      - Kirkwood to Matles Regarding Staff Finances, May 6, 1949; 12. (Box 7, Folder 75, Item 12)
      - Kirkwood Telegram to Matles Regarding Local 610 WABCO Strike Vote, May 10, 1949; 13. (Box 7, Folder 75, Item 13)
      - Kirkwood Telegram to Matles Regarding Factionalism and 1949 UE Convention Delegates Election, June 19, 1949; 14. (Box 7, Folder 75, Item 14)
      - Kirkwood to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, June 20, 1949; 15. (Box 7, Folder 75, Item 15)
      - Kirkwood to Emspak Regarding Unemployment, July 14, 1949; 16. (Box 7, Folder 75, Item 16)
      - Kirkwood to Fitzgerald Regarding Unemployment, July 20, 1949; 17. (Box 7, Folder 75, Item 17)
      - Kirkwood to Fitzgerald Regarding House Un-American Activities Committee, August 9, 1949; 18. (Box 7, Folder 75, Item 18)
      - Kirkwood to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, August 12, 1949; 19. (Box 7, Folder 75, Item 19)
      - Kirkwood to Matles Regarding 1949 UE Convention, August 19, 1949; 20. (Box 7, Folder 75, Item 20)
      - Kirkwood to Fitzgerald Regarding Staff Finances, August 29, 1949; 21. (Box 7, Folder 75, Item 21)
    - Local 610 Robert Kirkwood Outgoing Correspondence, October 3, 1949 - December 18, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 76)
      - Kirkwood to James Matles Regarding Factionalism, Local 610 Officers Election, Local 601 and Association of Catholic Trade Unionists with Election Results, October 3, 1949; 1. (Box 7, Folder 76, Item 1)
      - Kirkwood Telegram to Matles Regarding Radio Corporation of America Contract, October 24, 1949; 2. (Box 7, Folder 76, Item 2)
      - Kirkwood to Janet Barish Regarding Address, December 1, 1949; 3. (Box 7, Folder 76, Item 3)
      - Kirkwood to Matles Regarding Local 610 Westinghouse Air Brake Company Collective Bargaining, Wages, Pensions and IUE Inter-Union Rivalry, February 7, 1950; 4. (Box 7, Folder 76, Item 4)
      - Kirkwood to Matles Regarding Pensions and IUE Inter-Union Rivalry, February 27, 1950; 5. (Box 7, Folder 76, Item 5)
      - Kirkwood to Julius Emspak Regarding Staff Finances with Receipt and IOU, May 15, 1951; 6. (Box 7, Folder 76, Item 6)
      - Kirkwood to Emspak Regarding District Council and Factionalism with Kirkwood Letter to District 6, October 13, 1952; 7. (Box 7, Folder 76, Item 7)
      - Kirkwood to Emspak Regarding Strike Fund, October 21, 1952; 8. (Box 7, Folder 76, Item 8)
      - Kirkwood to Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism and District Council, October 28, 1952; 9. (Box 7, Folder 76, Item 9)
      - Kirkwood to Edward Matthews Regarding Wages and Westinghouse, November 3, 1952; 10. (Box 7, Folder 76, Item 10)
      - Kirkwood to Emspak Regarding Strike Fund, November 5, 1952; 11. (Box 7, Folder 76, Item 11)
      - Kirkwood to Emspak Regarding Strike Fund, December 18, 1952; 12. (Box 7, Folder 76, Item 12)
    - Local 610 Robert Kirkwood Outgoing Correspondence, February 12, 1953 - August 3, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 77)
      - Kirkwood to James Matles Regarding Wages and Wage Stabilization Board, February 12, 1953; 1. (Box 7, Folder 77, Item 1)
      - Kirkwood to Matles Regarding Stewards Council Meeting, February 18, 1953; 2. (Box 7, Folder 77, Item 2)
      - Kirkwood to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Finances and Local 601, March 10, 1953; 3. (Box 7, Folder 77, Item 3)
      - Kirkwood to Stanley Loney Regarding District 6 Council, May 29, 1953; 4. (Box 7, Folder 77, Item 4)
      - Kirkwood to Matles Regarding IUE Inter-Union Rivalry and Factionalism, July 13, 1953; 5. (Box 7, Folder 77, Item 5)
      - Kirkwood to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, July 24, 1953; 6. (Box 7, Folder 77, Item 6)
      - Kirkwood to Emspak Regarding Finances, July 31, 1953; 7. (Box 7, Folder 77, Item 7)
      - Kirkwood to Matles Regarding Local 610 Westinghouse Air Brake Company and Union Switch and Signal Contracts, January 26, 1954; 8. (Box 7, Folder 77, Item 8)
      - Kirkwood to Fitzgerald Regarding 1954 UE Convention, September 9, 1954; 9. (Box 7, Folder 77, Item 9)
      - Kirkwood to Matles Regarding Local 610 WABCO and Wages, November 8, 1954; 10. (Box 7, Folder 77, Item 10)
      - Kirkwood to Matles Regarding Wages and Local 610 WABCO Collective Bargaining, August 3, 1955; 11. (Box 7, Folder 77, Item 11)
    - Local 610 Albert Smith Incoming Correspondence, November 26, 1940 - January 4, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 78)
      - Janet Barish Regarding Staff Finances, January 4, 1946; 1. (Box 7, Folder 78, Item 1)
      - Neil Brant Telegram, March 13, 1941; 2. (Box 7, Folder 78, Item 2)
      - Brant Telegram, March 23, 1942; 3. (Box 7, Folder 78, Item 3)
      - Brant Telegram, March 25, 1942; 4. (Box 7, Folder 78, Item 4)
      - Brant Telegram, August 26, 1942; 5. (Box 7, Folder 78, Item 5)
      - Brant Telegram Regarding Arbitration, August 27, 1942; 6. (Box 7, Folder 78, Item 6)
      - Julius Emspak Regarding National Labor Relations Board, Janaury 18, 1941; 7. (Box 7, Folder 78, Item 7)
      - Emspak Regarding Supplies and Women's Auxiliary, March 27, 1941; 8. (Box 7, Folder 78, Item 8)
      - Emspak Regarding Kirkland Lake Gold Miners Strike, February 9, 1942; 9. (Box 7, Folder 78, Item 9)
      - Albert Fitzgerald Telegram, March 12, 1942; 10. (Box 7, Folder 78, Item 10)
      - James Matles Regarding NLRB with November 16, 1940, Winthrop Johns Letter to Matles, November 26, 1940; 11. (Box 7, Folder 78, Item 11)
      - Matles Regarding Stewards Council Meeting, December 27, 1940; 12. (Box 7, Folder 78, Item 12)
      - Matles Telegram, January 13, 1941; 13. (Box 7, Folder 78, Item 13)
      - Matles Telegram Regarding Organization, January 24, 1941; 14. (Box 7, Folder 78, Item 14)
      - Matles Regarding Arbitration and Crucible Steel, January 28, 1941; 15. (Box 7, Folder 78, Item 15)
      - Matles Regarding NLRB, January 29, 1941; 16. (Box 7, Folder 78, Item 16)
      - Matles Letter, February 4, 1941; 17. (Box 7, Folder 78, Item 17)
      - Matles Regarding General Electric, General Motors and Allis-Chalmers Contracts, February 4, 1941; 18. (Box 7, Folder 78, Item 18)
      - Secretary to Matles Regarding Westinghouse Air Brake Company, February 13, 1941; 19. (Box 7, Folder 78, Item 19)
      - Matles Letter, February 26, 1941; 20. (Box 7, Folder 78, Item 20)
      - Matles Regarding New York Airbrake, International Association of Machinists and Molders Union, March 6, 1941; 21. (Box 7, Folder 78, Item 21)
      - Matles Letter, March 7, 1941; 22. (Box 7, Folder 78, Item 22)
      - Matles Letter, March 20, 1941; 23. (Box 7, Folder 78, Item 23)